<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn C</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="desc">C is a procedural programming language. It was initially developed by Dennis Ritchie between 1969 and 1973.
        It was mainly developed as a system programming language to write operating system. … Like syntax of Java, PHP, JavaScript and many other languages is mainly based on C language.</string>
    <string name="player_error">Error initializing Youtube Player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
    <string name="c_in_out">As we all know the three essential functions of a computer are reading,
        processing and writing data.
        Majority of the programs take data as input,and then after processing the processed data is being displayed which is called information.
    In C programming you can use</string>
    <string name="c_install">As we all know the three essential functions of a computer are reading, processing and writing data. Majority of the programs take data as input,
    and then after processing the processed data is being displayed which is called information.
    In C programming you can use</string>
    <string name="c_struct">A C program involves the following sections:</string>
    <string name="fromat_specifier">Format specifiers can be defined as the operators which are used in association with printf() function for printing the data that is referred by any object or any variable.
        When a value is stored in a particular variable, then you cannot print the value stored in the variable straightforwardly without using the format specifiers.
        You can retrieve the data that are stored in the variables and can print them onto the console screen by implementing these format specifiers in a printf() function.
    Format specifiers start with a percentage</string>
    <string name="history_c"> programming
        language was developed to overcome the difficulties found in older programming languages
        such as BCPL, BASIC, B, etc.</string>
    <string name="limitation">Difficult to debug.
    C allows a lot of freedom in writing code, and that is why you can put an empty line or white space anywhere in the program.
        And because there is no fixed place to start or end the line, so it is difficult to read and understand the program.
    C compilers can only identify errors a</string>
    <string name="first_slide_text">
        If you think it is hard then just try to code in C.
    </string>
    <string name="scond_slide_text">
        Learning C is the fundamental to All programming language and it is most
        popular language to program  hardware.
    </string>

    <string name="third_slide_text">
        The software like Windows,Google Applications,MySQL Server,Apple-OS X etc are written purely in c

    </string>
    <!-- ##########################################################################################################-->
    <string name="prgm1">
      Celsius to Farenhite
  </string>

    <string name="prgm2">
        Convert To Celsius
    </string>
    <string name="prgm3">
        convert To km
    </string>
    <string name="prgm4">
        find Leap Year
    </string>
    <string name="prgm5">
        larger Of Two
    </string>
    <string name="prgm6">
        larger Of Two With Conditions
    </string>
    <string name="prgm7">
        meter to feet
    </string>
    <string name="prgm8">
        sum
    </string>

    <string name="prgm9">
        swap
    </string>
    <string name="prgm10">
        swap Two Numbers
    </string>
    <string name="pref_ad_removal_purchased">Item purchased</string>
    <string name="item_Consumed">item Consumed</string>
    <string name="key">
    
    </string>
</resources>
